I have four subjects in the Fall session, of which three are offered by the Information Systems Department. I will write about one in each text file that I create.
3. Advanced Data Management by Dr. Michael Dereszynski
I will gain a good working knowledge of Git, GitHub, Object Oriented Programming, and accessing as well as developing APIs. By the end of this subject, I want to gain intermediate level of knowledge of Python and Git. I want to get an A in this subject.